{
	"1": {
		"answer_false1": "1\u516c\u91cc/\u6642",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u822a\u901f\u7684\u55ae\u4f4d\u201c\u7bc0\u201d\u662f\u6307\uff08     \uff09",
		"answer_right": "1\u6d77\u6d6c/\u6642",
		"answer_false3": "1\u82f1\u91cc/\u6642",
		"answer_false2": "1\u7c73/\u6642",
		"id": 1
	},
	"2": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8266\u5c4b",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u8266\u8247\u4e0a\u64cd\u63a7\u8266\u548c\u6307\u63ee\u4f5c\u6230\u7684\u5730\u65b9\u88ab\u7a31\u70ba\uff08     \uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u8266\u6a4b",
		"answer_false3": "\u8266\u6d1e",
		"answer_false2": "\u8266\u623f",
		"id": 2
	},
	"3": {
		"answer_false1": "500",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u8896\u73cd\u6f5b\u8247\u7684\u6392\u6c34\u91cf\u5f80\u5f80\u5728\uff08     \uff09\u5678\u4ee5\u4e0b",
		"answer_right": "100",
		"answer_false3": "200",
		"answer_false2": "300",
		"id": 3
	},
	"4": {
		"answer_false1": "\u6642\u9593",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u6d77\u8ecd\u4e2d\u5e38\u7528\u55ae\u4f4d\u201c\u93c8\u201d\u662f\uff08     \uff09\u55ae\u4f4d",
		"answer_right": "\u9577\u5ea6",
		"answer_false3": "\u901f\u5ea6",
		"answer_false2": "\u91cd\u91cf",
		"id": 4
	},
	"5": {
		"answer_false1": "5.5",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u8f15\u5de1\u548c\u91cd\u5de1\u7684\u53e3\u5f91\u5283\u5206\u754c\u9650\u662f\uff08     \uff09\u82f1\u5bf8",
		"answer_right": "6.1",
		"answer_false3": "6.4",
		"answer_false2": "5.8",
		"id": 5
	},
	"6": {
		"answer_false1": "\u822a\u901f",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u8266\u548c\u8247\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u5283\u5206\u6a19\u6e96\u662f\uff08     \uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u5678\u4f4d",
		"answer_false3": "\u7e8c\u822a",
		"answer_false2": "\u8239\u54e1\u6578",
		"id": 6
	},
	"7": {
		"answer_false1": "\u8266\u88dd\u6a5f",
		"type": 1,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u5728\u822a\u7a7a\u6bcd\u8266\u4e0a\u8d77\u964d\u7684\u98db\u6a5f\u4e00\u822c\u7a31\u4f5c\u70ba\uff08     \uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u8266\u8f09\u6a5f",
		"answer_false3": "\u8266\u8239\u6a5f",
		"answer_false2": "\u822a\u6bcd\u6a5f",
		"id": 7
	},
	"8": {
		"answer_false1": "\u66b4\u64ca\u50b7\u5bb3",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u904a\u6232\u4e2d\u5728\u6230\u9b25\u6642\u70ae\u5f48\u9020\u6210\u7684\u50b7\u5bb3\u6578\u503c\u70ba\u7d2b\u8272\u8868\u793a\uff08     \uff09",
		"answer_right": "\u7a7f\u7532\u5f48\u50b7\u5bb3",
		"answer_false3": "\u9ad8\u7206\u5f48\u50b7\u5bb3",
		"answer_false2": "\u901a\u5e38\u5f48\u50b7\u5bb3",
		"id": 8
	},
	"9": {
		"answer_false1": "\u6a5f\u52d5",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u904a\u6232\u4e2d\u8f2a\u578b\u9663\u8b77\u885b\u9663\u578b\u6703\u63d0\u9ad8\uff08     \uff09\u5c6c\u6027",
		"answer_right": "\u9632\u7a7a",
		"answer_false3": "\u96f7\u64ca",
		"answer_false2": "\u70ae\u64ca",
		"id": 9
	},
	"10": {
		"answer_false1": "\u9020\u6210\u50b7\u5bb3\u589e\u52a0",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u904a\u6232\u4e2d\u5b89\u5168\u6d77\u57df\u6703\u63d0\u4f9b\uff08     \uff09\u7684buff\u6548\u679c",
		"answer_right": "\u53d7\u50b7\u6e1b\u514d",
		"answer_false3": "\u6e1b\u5c11\u6cb9\u8017",
		"answer_false2": "\u5c6c\u6027\u63d0\u9ad8",
		"id": 10
	},
	"11": {
		"answer_false1": "20",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u89f8\u767c\u660e\u77f3\u7372\u53d6\u4efb\u52d9\u9700\u8981\u5728\u5546\u5e97\u4e2d\u9ede\u64ca\uff08     \uff09\u6b21",
		"answer_right": "30",
		"answer_false3": "40",
		"answer_false2": "15",
		"id": 11
	},
	"12": {
		"answer_false1": "30.00%",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u904a\u6232\u4e2d\u8266\u968a\u5f48\u85e5\u5331\u4e4f\u5f8c\u6e1b\u5c11\u5176\uff08     \uff09\u7684\u50b7\u5bb3",
		"answer_right": "50.00%",
		"answer_false3": "60.00%",
		"answer_false2": "40.00%",
		"id": 12
	},
	"13": {
		"answer_false1": "2",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u904a\u6232\u958b\u767c\u8239\u5862\u4e2d\u7684\u65b9\u6848\u8266\u6700\u591a\u53ef\u540c\u6642\u7814\n\u7a76\uff08     \uff09\u8258",
		"answer_right": "1",
		"answer_false3": "4",
		"answer_false2": "3",
		"id": 13
	},
	"14": {
		"answer_false1": "20",
		"type": 2,
		"wrong_time": 300,
		"question": "\u5f8c\u5b85\u4e2d\u8cfc\u8cb7\u4e00\u500b\u6d77\u8ecd\u5496\u55b1\u6d88\u8017\uff08     \uff09\u77f3\u6cb9",
		"answer_right": "50",
		"answer_false3": "10",
		"answer_false2": "30",
		"id": 14
	},
	"all": [
		1,
		2,
		3,
		4,
		5,
		6,
		7,
		8,
		9,
		10,
		11,
		12,
		13,
		14
	]
}